http://www.rmhjax.org/internet_privacy_policy/index.html

Internet Privacy Policy
Ronald McDonald House Charities® of Jacksonville values our volunteers and donors and has the greatest respect for your privacy. Accordingly, we have set out the following policy as it pertains to gathering information.
Information Collected & How It Is Used
RMHC Jacksonville gathers personal information, such as first and last names, home addresses and email addresses, only when voluntarily submitted by you.
We may use personal information collected from you to send you updates and information about RMHC Jacksonville and our programs. If you prefer that you do not recieve those, please let us know.
RMHC Jacksonville does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties.
RMHC Jacksonville reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request in order to protect the integrity of the site, fulfill your requests or cooperate in any law enforcement investigation on a public safety matter.
If you make an online donation, personal information will be collected from you in order to process that donation. Your credit card information goes through PayPal's secure site and not to RMHC Jacksonville.
Access
You are in control of all personal information you provide to us online. If you would like to correct the personal information we have about you or if you would like to change your preferences for contact from us, let us know by contacting us.
Links To Other Sites
We offer links to sites that are not operated by RMHC Jacksonville. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy and other policies. We are not responsible for the policies and practices of other companies.
Contact Us
Staff
Board of Directors
2013 Discovery Circle Board
2013 Advisory Board
Internet Privacy Policy
All contents ©2013 McDonald's. All rights reserved.
Web Design powered by Msites.
Administrators: Login
